bmiresearch.com 2016-11-29

# Privacy Policy | BMI Research

## Privacy Statement for Business Monitor International Limited, trading as BMI Research

This web-site (the 'Site') is owned and operated by Business Monitor International Limited, trading as BMI Research who is also the data controller for the purposes of the Data Protection Act 1998 ('DPA').

Respecting and protecting your privacy is critical to Business Monitor International Limited, trading as BMI Research. The purpose of this Privacy Policy together with the Terms of Use is to set out the basis on which any personal data which we collect from the Site, or that you provide to us, will be processed by us and to ensure that we interact with you in line with current data protection legislation such as the DPA and in accordance with your wishes.

The Site is not intended for individuals under 16 years of age. Business Monitor International Limited, trading as BMI Research does not knowingly collect personal information from individuals under 16 via the Site.

**By accessing and viewing the Web Site, you agree to the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy.** In order to access certain portions of the Web Site you will be required to register by providing certain limited information regarding you and the company you represent and in doing so you consent to the collection, use and transfer of such information under the terms of this privacy policy.

## Registration

As mentioned above, in order to use many features of the Site, you will be asked to complete a registration form. During registration, you are required to provide contact information, for you and the company you represent as well as limited business information about the company you represent. Business Monitor International Limited, trading as BMI Research may use this contact information as a means of confirmation of your identity, position, or relationship to a particular company.

## Information Collection and Processing and Use From Registered Users

When you register on the Site, we will ask you to share limited information about yourself and the company you represent. Only disclose business information that you are authorised to disclose. We use this information to provide you with quality services as well as with offers that we think are relevant to you based on the preferences you share at registration. Please also see the 'Information Sharing and Disclosure' section below.

Using your contact information, Business Monitor International Limited, trading as BMI Research may also send you e-mail messages under the following circumstances, among others:

  * To respond to an inquiry or request for information; 
  * To thank you for contacting Business Monitor International Limited, trading as BMI Research; 
  * To welcome you to the Site and to its products and services; 
  * To explain new product offerings and features of our services; 
  * To notify you of special promotions; and 
  * To communicate with you regarding customer service related issues (including any changes to our service). 

In order to maintain accurate records concerning communications that Business Monitor International Limited, trading as BMI Research may have received from or sent to you, Business Monitor International Limited, trading as BMI Research may also indefinitely store any information that you provide to Business Monitor International Limited, trading as BMI Research through the Website. We may also collect and process details of your visits to the Site and the resources that you access.

## Information Sharing and Disclosure

If Business Monitor International Limited, trading as BMI Research or substantially all of its assets are acquired by a third party, in which case personal data held by it about its customers will be one of the transferred assets.

## Special Offers 

We do not provide copies of our email subscriber database information to third parties. As a Registered User and based on the preferences you share at registration, you will occasionally receive information on products, services, special deals and newsletters.

## Where We Store Your Information 

The data that we collect from you may be transferred to, and stored at, a destination outside the European Economic Area ('EEA'). It may also be processed by staff operating outside the EEA who work for us or for one of our suppliers. Such staff maybe engaged in the provision of support services. By submitting your personal data, you agree to this transfer, storing or processing. Business Monitor International Limited, trading as BMI Research will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this privacy policy.

Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure. Although we will do our best to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee the security of your information transmitted to the Site; any transmission is at your own risk. Once we have received your information, we will use strict procedures and security features to try to prevent unauthorised access.

## Links to Other Web Sites 

The Site contains links to other web sites of our partner networks, sponsors, advertisers and affiliates ('Partners'). Please be aware that Business Monitor International Limited, trading as BMI Research is not responsible for the privacy practices of other sites. This privacy policy applies solely to information collected by this website.

## Cookies 

A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's hard drive containing information about the user. Usage of cookies is for the convenience of visitors. For instance, by setting a cookie on our site, the user would not have to log in a password more than once, thereby saving time while on our site. If a user rejects the cookie, they may still use our site.

Cookies can also enable us to track and target the interests of our users in order to enhance the experience on our site. Some of our business partners use cookies on our site (for example, advertisers). However, we have no access to, or control over, these cookies.

## Log Files 

We use IP addresses to analyse trends, administer the Site, track user's movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses that we collect are not linked to personally identifiable information.

## Your Rights 

The DPA gives you the right to access information held about you. Your right of access can be exercised in accordance with the DPA. Any access request may be subject to a fee of £10 to meet our costs in providing you with details of the information we hold about you.

## Notification of Policy Changes 

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will seek to advise all users of these changes.

## Updating Personal Information 

You may update or correct information you previously provided to Business Monitor International Limited, trading as BMI Research by accessing your user profile on the Site.

## Choice/Opt-out 

Our users are given the opportunity to 'opt-out' of having their information used for purposes not directly related to our site at the point where we ask for the information. Users who no longer wish to receive a newsletter/alert/briefing etc. may opt-out of receiving these communications by replying to the unsubscribe link in the e-mail

## Questions or Comments Regarding the Privacy Policy 

For additional questions, or to be taken off our marketing lists, please send an e-mail to [marketing@bmiresearch.com](mailto:marketing@bmiresearch.com)
